{
    "001" : {"question" : "Which one of these characters is not friends with Harry Potter?", 
             "options" : ["Ron Weasley", "Neville Longbottom", "Draco Malfoy", "Hermione Granger"], 
             "answer" : "Draco Malfoy"},
    "002" : {"question" : "What is the color of Donald Duck’s bowtie?", 
             "options" : ["Red", "Yellow", "Blue", "White"], 
             "answer" : "Red"},
    "003" : {"question" : "What was the name of the band Lionel Richie was a part of?", 
             "options" : ["King Harvest", "Spectrums", "Commodores", "The Marshall Tucker Band"], 
             "answer" : "Commodores"},
    "004" : {"question" : "Which animal does not appear in the Chinese zodiac?", 
             "options" : ["Dragon", "Rabbit", "Dog", "Hummingbird"], 
             "answer" : "Hummingbird"},
    "005" : {"question" : "Which country held the 2016 Summer Olympics?", 
             "options" : ["China", "Ireland", "Brazil", "Italy"], 
             "answer" : "Brazil"},
    "006" : {"question" : "Which planet is the hottest?", 
             "options" : ["Venus", "Saturn", "Mercury", "Mars"], 
             "answer" : "Venus"},
    "007" : {"question" : "What does the “D” in “D-Day” stand for?", 
             "options" : ["Dooms", "Dark", "Denmark ", "Dunkirk"], 
             "answer" : "Dunkirk"},
    "008" : {"question" : "In Pirates of the Caribbean, what was Captain Jack Sparrow’s ship’s name?", 
             "options" : ["The Marauder", "The Black Pearl", "The Black Python", "The Slytherin"], 
             "answer" : "The Black Python"},
    "009" : {"question" : "According to Forrest Gump, “life was like…”", 
             "options" : ["A bag of lemons", "A handful of roses", "A lollipop", "A box of chocolates"], 
             "answer" : "A box of chocolates"},
    "010" : {"question" : "The British band One Direction (rip) was made up of Harry, Louis, Niall, Zayn, and…", 
             "options" : ["Paul", "Callum", "Kevin", "Liam"], 
             "answer" : "Liam"},
    "011" : {"question" : "What is the rarest blood type?", 
             "options" : ["O", "A", "B", "AB-Negative"], 
             "answer" : "AB-Negative"},
    "012" : {"question" : "Holly Golightly is a character in which film?", 
             "options" : ["Breakfast at Tiffanys", "Pretty In Pink", "Funny Face", "Singing In The Rain"], 
             "answer" : "Breakfast at Tiffanys"},
    "013" : {"question" : "In The Wizard of Oz, the Tin Man wanted to see the Wizard about getting…", 
             "options" : ["A brain", "An oil can", "A dog", "A heart"], 
             "answer" : "A heart"},
    "014" : {"question" : "Which one of these characters isn’t a part of the Friends group?", 
             "options" : ["Rachel", "Joey", "Gunther", "Monica"], 
             "answer" : "Gunther"},
    "015" : {"question" : "How many bones are there in the human body?", 
             "options" : ["206", "205", "201", "209"], 
             "answer" : "206"},
    "016" : {"question" : "Fe is the chemical symbol for…", 
             "options" : ["Zinc", "Hydrogen", "Fluorine", "Iron"], 
             "answer" : "Iron"}             
}